<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="power_settings_instructions">Enabling STAMINA mode in Power management will optimise battery lifetime</string>
    <string name="battery_low_title">Please connect charger</string>
    <string name="usb_device_permission_prompt">Allow the application %1$s to access the USB device?</string>
    <string name="usb_accessory_permission_prompt">Allow the application %1$s to access the USB accessory?</string>
    <string name="usb_accessory_uri_prompt">No installed applications work with this USB accessory. Learn more about this accessory at %1$s</string>
    <string name="compat_mode_help_header">Compatibility Zoom</string>
    <string name="screenshot_saving_ticker">Saving screenshot…</string>
    <string name="screenshot_saving_title">Saving screenshot…</string>
    <string name="installer_cd_button_title">Install Android File Transfer application for Mac</string>
    <string name="unmount_strings_dialog_content_txt">Do not remove the SD card while it is disconnecting</string>
    <string name="accessibility_state_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="status_bar_autorotate">Auto-rotate</string>
    <string name="status_bar_autosync_dialog_disable_title">Turn auto-sync data off?</string>
    <string name="status_bar_autosync_dialog_disable_warning">"This will conserve data and battery usage, but you'll need to sync each account manually to collect recent information. And you won't receive notifications when updates occur."</string>
    <string name="status_bar_autosync_dialog_enable_title">Turn on auto-sync data?</string>
    <string name="status_bar_autosync_dialog_enable_warning">"Any changes you make to your accounts on the web will be automatically copied to your phone.



Some accounts may also automatically copy any changes you make on the phone to the web. A Google Account works this way.



To select what type of information to sync within each account, go to Settings > Accounts."</string>
    <string name="status_bar_autosync_dialog_extended_enable_warning">"Any changes you make to your accounts on the web will be automatically copied to your device.

Some accounts may also automatically copy any changes you make on the device to the web. A Google Account works this way.

To select what type of information to sync within each account, go to Settings > Accounts.

Data transmission charges may apply when updates are made to your device. An unlimited data plan is recommended."</string>
    <string name="status_bar_settings_autorotate">Auto-rotate screen</string>
</resources>
